What is bigfoot?
We will find out today.
For several years, people around the world have been fascinated by the legend of Bigfoot.
Several people have talked about their meetings with the hairy beast.
A large and hairy alar -like creature that goes on two legs.
But even though there is no definitive evidence of Bigfoot's existence, new reports on possible meetings with Bigfoot continue to emerge even today.
Today we will dive into the legend of Bigfoot to go through the most famous ...
And perhaps most convincingly so -called "evidence" and hopefully get an answer to the question that everyone is asking.
Is Bigfoot for real?
In this video we will go through the following things:
What is the evidence?
And finally.. Is Bigfoot for real or is everything a scam?
What is bigfoot?
Bigfoot is a large alar -like creature that is said to be in the forests in North America.
It goes on two legs, which we humans do and have a dark coat.
The body should be very muscular and broad -axled.
The length of Bigfoot is somewhere between 2-3 meters.
Bigfoot leaves large human -like footprints behind.
Hence the name..bigfoot
Those who are said to have seen Bigfoot say that the face has character traits similar to a person's but that it also resembles a gorillas.
Bigfoot should also have a very unpleasant and peculiar smell.
A stench that feels at a very long distance.
Bigfoot is what is called a cryptozoolological creature.
It is a collective name for a number of different animal species that have not been proven by science.
Examples of these are Storsjöodjuret, Loch Ness beast, Chupacabra, Yeti [Snowman] and others.
The most common theory that flourishes about bigfoot is that it is a kind of undetected species of a primate.
An alar -like creature, but still more intelligent and developed than any other primate that we know.
After that, more people in the workplace began to tell us that they had also seen similar footsteps and that they had been involved in inexplicable events in the workplace.
Among other things, an oil barrel that should have weighed over 200 kg had disappeared for a day without any explanation.
Some of the workers also told me that they felt observed sometimes when they worked late in the evenings ...
The casts were made of the footprints and they turned out that the footprints were about 40 cm long.
Hence the natural name of the creature that made these footsteps ... Bigfoot.
It didn't take long before the history of a large and hairy best that left large footsteps began to spread in the United States, first from mouth to mouth and then from newspaper to newspaper.
In October, 1958, the footprints were on the first page of the local news magazine.
Soon, the rumor of Bigfoot had spread throughout the country.
What is the evidence?
What evidence do we have for Bigfoot's existence?
What we talked about was exactly the footprints at the River Bluff Creek.
However, these are not the only footprints.
The news quickly spread to several major American news channels BBC, CNN, ABC News and Fox News, among other things.
In fact, the hunters had even been supported by a researcher that it could very well be Bigfoot.
But was it real?
We go through it in a little while.
First, we have to look at other so -called evidence.
There are actually several occasions where people have managed to get Bigfoot on film.
I thought we were looking at 4 of them.
The first film shows "Bigfoot" which goes among the bushes and then it picks up its child in its arms and goes out of the picture.
Some claim that this is a clear proof that Bigfoot actually exists while others say
That it is simply just a man with a gorilla costume.
The second movie is from 2011 when a family is up among the mountains, unfortunately it is unknown where they were.
They let the son practice sniper and a helicopter floats above them while this happens.
When the young boy on the movie shoots a shot, you can see something moving on the right of the movie.
What is running over there among the bushes?
It moves very humanly but unfortunately it is too far away to say exactly what it is.
Was it scared of the shot?
Who knows.
The family was obviously wondering why the helicopter was there, but now they believe it chased Bigfoot.
Third film, filmed by an unknown person on December 29, 2009 in Carbondale Pennsylvania.
The person in the video walks around the woods on the back of their house after hearing noise out there.
At 41 seconds into the video, Bigfoot shows up among the trees.
What differs from the other films is that Bigfoot is white.
A so -called Albino Bigfoot.
The fourth movie, the movie that is perhaps best known.
It was filmed by Roger Patterson in 1967 when he was to film a documentary about Bigfoot on the River Bluff Creek.
Let's look.
And now that all these different evidence has proven to be a scam, it was perhaps thought that the legend of Bigfoot would die out.
But that did not happen.
The news The various bluffs were ignored by the Bigfoot enthusiasts and the interest in Bigfoot has instead become even greater.
Today, there are clubs and organizations in the United States whose sole purpose is to search for bigfoot.
A little strange how we humans work sometimes ..
Although the name Bigfoot became known in 1958 in the United States, legends on various large human -like creatures have been around for centuries in the rest of the world.
For example, Yeti, also called the snowman who is said to live up in the Himalayan Mountains.
We have the Russian creature Menk, which is Russia's version of a Yeti you can say.
Mongolia is said to have a creature called Almas.
Vietnam has Nguoi Rung.
Indonesia has EBU Gogo.